<color=\"1,0,0\">___________________
Save Terrain Paste Buffer
___________________</color>


Possibility to save 5 copied terrain buffers and load again in the paste clipboard. 
This function is important, if You want to Cover Terrain With Water (see menu "Change").

<color=\"1,1,1\">First step: </color>
click on the <icon=\"(18)(icons/Editor Copy")\"> Terrain Copy icon and select the terrain.

<color=\"1,1,1\">Second step: </color>
To save the Terrain just click on one of the five Radio Buttons under <u>Save</u>.

The terrain buffers will be saved in the <color=\"0,1,1\">data</color> folder as <color=\"0,1,1\">*.TLB</color> files (1-5.TLB)

If you want to load one the terrain buffers that you have already saved, just click on one of the five Radio Buttons under <u>Load</u> and then you can paste the loaded terrain to the map.

<color=\"0.9,0.7,0.9\">NOTE: Notice that in the "Save Terrain" Text Box that at the very top is a <icon=\"(18)(icons/Editor Copy")\"> Terrain Copy icon, so you can go back and copy another Terrain right from there is you wish.</color>
		


