<color=\"1,0,0\">______
Change
______</color>

In this menu one can change the terrain of the entire map.
On the left three Dropdown menues are the land terrains, on the right ones the waterbodies. 
Select one, and the entire map is filled with the chosen terrain/water.

<color=\"1,1,1\">Paint Water Low: </color>
The entire map will get flattened and covered with the groundterrain of a waterbody. The "water" is passable for land units.

<color=\"1,1,1\">Paint Water Medium/High: </color>
The entire map will get flattened and covered with the waterbody in a medium/bigger depth. The "water" is not passable, only water units can move.

To define your own height/depth, put in the <link="topic:Commands">Console</link> the command
<color=\"0,1,0\">uiCoverTerrainWithWater(Height,Depth,"Water Name")</color>

<color=\"1,1,1\">Smooth Fast</color>
Button for flatten all the terrain quick: the entire map get flattened.
<color=\"0,1,1\">Caution on maps with waterbodies: they will flatten too!</color>

<color=\"1,1,1\">Smooth Slow</color>
Button for smoothing all the terrain: each left mouse click will flatten the entire map a little bit.

<color=\"1,1,1\">Selection</color>
<color=\"1,1,0\">Smooth Fast</color>
Opens the “Modify Terrain” mode: paint a half (invisible) square with the cursor (left mouse key) and press the button "Smooth Fast" again, the selected area will get flattened quick.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Smooth Slow</color>
The same, but the selected area will flatten slowly.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Done</color>
For leaving the “Modify Terrain” mode when one has finished. 

 