<color=\"1,0,0\">_________
Pitch Editor 
_________</color>

If "Camera Limit" is Off, the Pitch & Zoom won´t work, but you can move the camera unlimited with the keyboard hotkeys <color=\"0,1,1\">Page Up, Page Down, a, z</color> or the menu "View" buttons.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Pitch</color>
15 buttons from -60 to +135 will change the camera pitch immediately
A negative pitch automatically starts a special zoom (making it possible to zoom in) which you must change manually to a positive Pitch eventually (Zoom Normal).

<u>For negative pitch -20:</u> you're going to have to zoom in for 10x, 
<u>for pitch –10</u> zoom in maximal (the normal minZoom 50), because at negative pitch the camera is actually below the map, so you'll see a black screen. Use the "normal" view or the - / + buttons to adjust view.
If you have trouble, press the “Pitch + Zoom Normal” button and load some Pitch again.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Min Zoom</color>
2 buttons for Minimal Zoom: 
with 20  it is possible to zoom in near the surface of the map, and 
with 5 it´s possible to zoom through the textures.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Max Zoom</color>
Dropdown menu for changing the Maximal Zoom for a larger map view:
open the Camera Editor and select the value from the dropdown list.
For changing the Zoom press the <icon=\"(18)(ui/minimize_noalpha")\"> key.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Reset at Camera Limit On</color>
To go back to the normal zoom/pitch press the <color=\"1,1,1\">Z Normal/P Normal</color> button.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Reset at Camera Limit Off</color>
Press the <icon=\"(18)(icons/editor zoomnormal")\"> button to go back to the normal view or leave the CameraLimitOff modus with the check button.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Camera Limit</color> (works only with TT)
Default=On
Check button for switch on/off the Camera Limit. 
If the limit is off, one can use the hotkeys <color=\"0,1,1\">a, z</color> to change the camera pitch, the hotkeys <color=\"0,1,1\">page up/down</color> for move the camera up/down.
The pitch and zoom buttons won´t work.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Camera Rotate</color>
Default=On
Check button for switch on/off the Camera Rotate modus. If the modus is Off, one cannot rotate the camera.

<color=\"1,1,0\">Graphic Details</color>

3 buttons + 0 - for change the graphic textures details. Low will minimize the camera lag at lower pitches.
