<color=\"1,0,0\">_________
SOUNDSET
_________</color>

For setting a sound during the execution of animation of an object one selects the concerned object, opens the <color=\"1,1,1\">Animation View, "ALT+A," </color>and picks out procedure by clicking on the <color=\"1,1,1\">"Type" </color>button. 

In order to be able to set a sound, one must click on the button <color=\"1,1,1\">"Tag Type" </color>and then select the CheckButton <color=\"1,1,1\">"Sound Set"</color>. After confirmation appears with <color=\"1,1,1\">"SET:<none.(0.00) </color>in the left field. 
Click on that text line, (the writing becomes <color=\"0,0,1\">blue</color>), and it opens the right field with the Sound Set Dialogue and the drop down list (Set:).

After selecting a suitable sound (the Sound Name appears in the left field in place of "SET:<none>0.00") the marking will be changed to whatever you have chosen in the SET: Dropdown list. 

Then select your checkbox choices from the following:
- <color=\"1,1,1\">CheckVisible: </color>the sound is played only if the object is visible.
- <color=\"1,1,1\">CheckOwner: </color>the sound is played only if the object is in player's own possession.
- <color=\"1,1,1\">Loop: </color>a sound loop is produced, the sound constantly repeats themselves. 
- <color=\"1,1,1\">SendToAction: </color>doesn't function probably?

<color=\"1,0,1\">TAG</color>
The Tag appears after setting a sound underneath the slider bar (a small +) and indicates the beginning of an existing sound, if this was selected (writing becomes blue in the Tag Type gray box.). If the time is set to 0.00, then the sound starts with the beginning of the animation and the tag stands completely left. One can change this value, in which one 
<color=\"1,1,0\">- Either presses the key "Tag" at the correct time 
- And/or the time slowly adjusts with the keys + and/or -. </color>
If the animation is individually moved forward (with the <icon=\"(18)(icons\icon camera step forward")\"> button), the marking can set to be accurate with the correct picture. 
In each case SET must be selected <color=\"0,0,1\">(blue writing)</color>.

Also you can set several sounds per animation (<color=\"1,1,1\">ADD</color>) or be removed again (<color=\"1,1,1\">REMOVE</color>). Several sounds run off parallel.

With <color=\"1,0,1\">PROPAGATE</color> a marking attitude can get transferred on a variation of this animation (if available). Then the message 
<color=\"0,1,0\">"Propagated x tags to y potential animation nodes"</color> 
appears. Otherwise you will get an error message.

<color=\"1,0,1\">SAVE</color>
For storing the sounds in the animation text file (for example the "Villager Greek_anim.txt" example file that came with this zipfile) press the button "<color=\"1,1,1\">Save Tags </color>". If the text file of this animation is not in the folder AoM/anim, then a message
<color=\"0,1,0\"> "Could not save tag data...." </color>
appears and the changed animation is buffered in the file <temporary_anim.txt> in the folder AoM/anim.
It is advisable to check the "Window" CheckButton, to open this file and to save as "Villager Greek_anim.txt" for example. If the text file concerned is under the file name of the object in the folder AoM/anim/ the message 
<color=\"0,1,0\">"Tags successfully updated" </color>
appears and a backup text file (*.bak) is also created. 
In other words: you must have the text file in the anim folder. To retrieve any of the AOM animated text files just extract them from the "anim2.bar" file, with a program such as Aomed and put them in the anim folder. Then it will be available for changes. To use Aomed look at the readme that comes with Aomed.

<color=\"1,1,1\">ATK:</color> Attack, an additional sound SET can be added. 

<color=\"1,1,1\">SND:</color> Sound, to open the sound Browser the text field select and press the input key and/or any key. No further data. Probably doesn't function. 
